(Howard:)Hey, guys,
guess who's back from space.
(All:)Not now!
Oh, ow! Blueberry in my nose!
Blueberry in my nose!
(Leonard:)Snort it down and keep eating!
(Waitress:)You look familiar.
(Penny:)I don't think so.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Waitress:)I just saw you on the news.
(Waitress:)You're an astronaut.
(Dr Schneider:)Yes. Yes, I am.
(Waitress:)Good for you. How about a piece
of cheesecake on the house?
(Howard:)Oh, thank you so much.
I've been having the worst night.
(Howard:)I just got back and my friends don't care,
my wife's sick.
- Went to my mom's...
- You want the cheesecake or not?
(Howard:)Yes, please.
And I think it's gonna be a long, long time
Till touchdown brings me round again to find
(Howard:)I'm not the man they think I am at home
Oh, no, oh, no
(Howard:)I'm a rocket man
(Howard:)Perfect.